Daemons of the Shadow Realm
Akio-kun was a traitor?
Yup. He tried to kill Asa.
He was probably talked
into it by an outsider.
When the master returned,
we were supposed to extract
information from him and kill him.
Why does Dad always jump
right to killing people?
We lived and worked together.
Why can't he look for
a way to let him live?
It's just not possible.
Still feel like letting Akio live?
It's Kawai, the gardener.
His Daemons are strays now
that their master's dead.
Will someone form a contract with them?
Uh, may I?
They were close with my Heave-Ho.
I think they'd be compatible.
Excuse me.
Pair name, Gokko-Itachi.
Currently no individual names.
Previous master, Kawai Sanosuke.
He was killed while trying to
stop Kuroya Akio from escaping.
There you have it.
But he was like family.
Why would he kill him?
The police would enter the manor
to investigate an unnatural death.
We'll have to say he disappeared.
I brought in Kawai. He had no family.
It'll be easy to make him disappear.
Jin-kun!
You can't do this!
He worked for us for years.
We have to give him a proper funeral.
It'd be too sad not to, Dad!
Dad!
Wasn't it your strictness that
made Akio-kun close himself off?
You treat people like family
but don't hesitate to cut them
out when something happens.
You kill people for
opposing you even once.
If you'd been less rigid
and opened your heart,
maybe he would've told us why
he betrayed the Kagemori clan.
Maybe he wouldn't have
taken that last step.
Maybe Kawai-san wouldn't have died.
Hikaru!
You know, Sensei-chan...
I like your manga because there
aren't any bad people in them.
Reality sucks, so reading your
manga makes me feel safe.
The people in your worlds
wouldn't try to get rid of me.
But reality sucks.
It's full of unbelievably
shitty people, including me.
Despite being a piece of shit,
I want to protect the Kagemori
clan because it's where I belong.
I want you to keep drawing your
happy manga in a safe place.
I want Asa to live a
peaceful and normal life.
Akio chose the parents who abandoned him
over the Kagemoris and betrayed us.
I don't know how important
they are to him,
but I won't forgive anyone who tries
to destroy the place where we belong.
I'd even kill my own parents
if they tried to do that!
You can be lenient with shitheads and
hope they'll change, but they rarely do.
Kill them before it's too late.
That's all you can do.
I'm sorry.
Asa?
Don't leave Asa-san by herself.
I know!
Damn it, Asa! Wait!
Hey, Haruo.
Why do humans betray their friends?
Daemons never betray their partners.
Asa, you can't go off by yourself!
Akio might still be hiding somewhere!
Asa...
Akio-san, why?
You could've just tried to kill me.
Kawai-san wasn't a combatant.
He was just a gardener
who never killed anyone.
He never wished for anyone to die.
He was just living a normal life.
It's my fault.
Idiot!
Like hell it is!
It was the people trying to
exploit your power who did this!
It's not your fault, Asa!
Even Yuru said to stop
apologizing for everything!
The next time you apologize for some
dumb shit, I'll kick your ass!
I mean, I already did!
Sorry, Gabby-chan.
Episode 24
Higashi Village
and Nishino Village
What did I just say?!
Father's not here.
I'm alone.
I have to clean this up by myself.
This bandit was trying to kill me.
Don't hesitate. Don't waver.
Father's not here.
Nobody will clean this up for me.
I have to do it myself.
In the mountains...
I'm alone.
Huh? Where am I?
Oh, right. I was sleeping in the
place where they store... futons...
Are you feeling better, Yuru?
Don't scare me like that, Left!
What are you doing there?
Watching over you.
I still have some trouble moving, but I
can watch you forever from this posture.
Hup.
S-Sure, thanks.
Yuru-san, you're awake. How do you feel?
My body feels lighter. What time is it?
It's past noon.
Good morning.
Or good afternoon, I guess.
Your color's back.
Yuru-niichan, are you okay?
How's your shoulder?
And your fever?
You're feeling better? Good.
What was that for?
Did you sleep well?
I had an unpleasant dream.
Yeah? Have something good
to eat and forget about it.
All right. Let's get a late lunch going.
We can all eat together.
Took you long enough, Jin-chan.
Could you clean this up?
Are they Higashi Village agents?
Apparently. They killed Asa.
She gained the power of Break.
I'm sorry... Jin-san.
I'm sorry you have to clean this up.
I'm sorry.
It's all right. It's my job to clean up.
You don't need to apologize.
Let me handle the rest.
Take a mental break.
Gabby-chan, you're heavy.
Did you sleep well?
I had a bad dream.
Yeah? Have something to
eat and forget about it.
Is there anything in the kitchen?
Good morning. Or good afternoon, I guess.
Natsuki-neesan, were you guarding me?
They might strike again while our
guard's down after that incident.
I'm glad nothing happened.
Were you up all night?
Yeah. I'm going to take a shower.
Take over for me, Gabby-chan.
Sure thing.
Natsuki-neesan.
I'm so—
Thank you.
Once I'm out of the shower,
we're doing math lessons as usual.
What?!
At least let her rest today!
All-nighters are bad for
your skin, Natsuki-chan.
You should sleep a little, Natsuki.
Yeah! Go to sleep, Natsuki-nee!
Fine.
I'll get plenty of sleep once you've
finished your math for the day.
Hurry up and solve those
problems so I can sleep.
You're a monster!
Easy
Mathematics I
I wonder if I could
"Break" these problems.
Don't use a legendary
Daemon on crap like that!
Daemons of the Shadow Realm
Natsuki.
Jin-san said to take
the rest of the day off.
Haruo, let's drink together.
We'll drink and sleep first.
Then we'll think about Akio.
Staying up all night and drinking?
That's hell on your skin, Natsuki.
I'll put you to sleep
right now, Haruo.
Don't.
All right!
What's he doing?
He got an electronic dictionary.
I gave it to him so he can look
up words he doesn't know.
Since coming down here,
m 0 0 l 200 0 200 110 0 110
tsugai [noun]
1) When two or more objects combine to
form a pair
2) A male and female pair of animals
A couple
3) A hinge or joint
4) An opportunity, chance, or catalyst
I've encountered lots of words
I can read but don't understand.
Now I don't have to ask
people all the time.
I see. You're using hiragana input mode.
Okay.
Yuru-san, what did you
study in the village?
I read the texts Dera-san brought
from the outside world,
like Sun Tzu.
That's amazing, Yuru-san!
You're an educated barbarian!
I only said I read it.
I never said I understood it.
Uh, what? How does this work?
I'm not sure either,
but that's what it does.
Here.
Thank you.
Azami, you must be confused after
coming down here so suddenly.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I don't know what's going on,
but I've been confused for so long that
I've gotten used to being confused.
I know exactly what you mean!
Also, the rice is good.
Right?
Also, the cold box is amazing.
I'm glad Azami-chan's
feeling a little better.
The cold box?
Yeah.
Oh, the cold box.
But she probably wants to
go back to the village.
Yeah.
Right.
It's full of food.
That's amazing.
Yeah, it's amazing.
Yup.
I hope Mom's okay.
The ice doesn't taste good, though.
Cheer up.
You'll drive away all your
luck by looking so gloomy.
Right and Left.
Did you reattach your limbs?
Yup, good as new.
We're still not in top shape, though.
The stone adhesive Dera
bought worked well.
Stone Adhesive King
Super Strong!!
With this stuff, we can get cut
all we want, no problem.
Try not to get cut if you can avoid it.
Huh?
By the way, where's Dera-san?
Hey, buddy. Did you lose?
You, too?
I was trying to earn money
to support the kids.
I'm trying to pay off some debt.
I even took out a loan
so I could place a bet.
We'll make up for it with the
next race for your kids.
Yeah.
Scumbags.
Time to take out another loan!
Yamitsuki Milk
Hana
Oh, man.
Yikes.
Danno
Higashi Village's agents
have been summoned.
They're calling everyone
with an official role.
This message is from the bandits.
What? Them?
They're definitely planning
to put you through the wringer
for the Fujimurayama warehouse incident
and demand we hand over Yuru-kun.
Yup.
Do I need to go teach
all of them a lesson?
You can't.
Yeah, listen to Left.
We haven't fully recovered yet,
so we can't go.
It's not fair for you to
go hunting by yourself.
I see.
Then we'll all go teach them
a lesson once you're better.
Don't make it sound like
a fun little outing!
Don't. A lot of Higashi Village agents
with official roles are Daemon Wielders.
Which is why I won't be attending.
No fair, Dera-san!
If I skip, too, they'll be suspicious!
Hey. How's it going?
Hey, gravedigger.
Good to see you, Hana-chan.
You're still alive, huh?
Have you heard from Tadera?
Nope. He's not here?
Nah. He won't even respond
to messages. He's gone dark.
Really? I wonder if he's
got something to hide.
I ran into him at the
Fujimurayama warehouse.
He said he wouldn't hand over
Yuru or help Higashi Village.
So he betrayed Higashi Village?
I bet he's planning to use
the Seal kid for himself.
Wow, he sucks.
We'd better teach that turd
a lesson if we find him.
She really hates him.
The president's here.
Is everyone here?
Tadera's missing.
Figures.
Good evening.
Good to see you again.
Hey, it's a message from Jiro.
president's daemons well
President?
He's the leader of Higashi
Village's agents down here.
He's the one who assigns us work,
so I'd rather not fight him,
but he also wants to
acquire Break and Seal
so Higashi Village can
take over the world.
I heard Tadera Ryu has taken Yuru
and gone into hiding, gravedigger.
Yeah, apparently.
You haven't heard from him?
Like I told the bandits,
I just brought Yuru-kun down the mountain
and dropped them off
near Dera-san's place.
I haven't heard from them since.
Why didn't you tell us you brought
Yuru out of the village?
It's a good thing we heard
about it through the shaman.
We almost didn't hear about
Higashi Village being attacked.
Hey, don't blame me!
Dera-san didn't tell me anything either!
Right.
Higashi Village is a mess
after the Kagemoris attacked,
Asa is with the Kagemoris and
has already acquired Break,
and Yuru is down here.
The bandits were nearly wiped out.
The shaman and Tadera are gone.
Almost everyone who knew the way through
the Higashi Village barrier is gone,
which means waiting for instructions
from Granny Yamaha will slow us down.
From now on, I should
take command down here.
president ulterior motives
Ulterior motives?
Huh? What? For Hana-chan?
She'll kill that perv!
wants to take over higashi village
Oh, that kind of ulterior motive. Whew.
First, find Tadera and track down Yuru.
What if he resists?
He doesn't have Daemons. We can
just throw combat Daemons at him.
Jiro?
What is that?
They're not...
potentially dangerous objects.
Are these Daemon relics?
They're Daemons.
They're active.
We sense souls inside them.
Whose Daemons are these?
What were they doing here?
Who knows?
Someone form a contract with them.
Translator:
Sho Stifler
Timer:
Edgar Cruz
Editor:
Salem Alabanza
Quality Control:
Gabriella Alabanza
Final Quality Control:
Michelle Tymon
There's someone who infects Daemon
relics and blows them up?
Do you know anything?
I have no information
on anyone like that.
A Daemon unknown to us?
Let's have everyone in the manor check
if their Daemons have been infected.
Bunbun thinks it might be
a Daemon from the West.
The West?
The West? Perhaps...
No, it couldn't be.
Nishino Village was destroyed.
It sits at the bottom of a reservoir.
Nishino Village